<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/</link><description>Recent content on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://minecrafttas.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/rules/</guid><description>Do NOT talk about your submission, whether it&amp;rsquo;s your time, strats or anything else. Not even a hint that you found the best strat ever. Do NOT leak the task to non participants, bystanders will discuss new strats that participants can use as an advantage. You may resubmit a run within the submission period. The submission has to follow the task rules to be valid. Organisers may point out rule breaks so you can resubmit a valid run, but don&amp;rsquo;t always count on that.</description></item><item><title>Task 1</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task1/</guid><description>Announced on 18.11.2020
From now on, any strat leaking will result in disqualification, also do not talk about the tasks outside of tc-general-task1
Tomb Destroyer%
Task: Destroy every (coloured) terracotta block in and outside a desert temple.
Version: 1.12.2
Seed: -2579494896997723047
Additional Information:
You don&amp;rsquo;t need to collect the terracotta blocks, just destroy them. It is not allowed to manipulate the gear of zombies and skeletons (Or any other mob) to get op gear right at the start of the game.</description></item><item><title>Task 2</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task2/</guid><description>Announced on 02.12.2020
Start a bakery%
Task: Create all baked goods in Minecraft (cake, cookie, piece of bread, pumpkin pie) without the use of villagers
Version: 1.12.2
Start on the world file below
Additional Information:
Glitchless! Duping is not allowed, except duping buckets, to make it not too long. You are allowed to dupe either empty buckets or filled buckets. It is not allowed to abuse invulnerability frames after joining It is not allowed to manipulate the gear of zombies and skeletons (Or any other mob) to get op gear right at the start of the game.</description></item><item><title>LoTAS</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/downloads/non-playback/lotas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/downloads/non-playback/lotas/</guid><description>A non-playback mod for version 1.8.9-1.18.1
Features Tickratechanger Tickrate 0/Pause server and client Item duplication (Duping) Savestates Drop Manipulation Dragon Manipulation Spawn Manipulation Ingame timer And more!</description></item><item><title>Task 3</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task3/</guid><description>Announced on 12.03.2021
Stack of Lime Wool%
Task: Obtain a stack of lime wool set seed glitched
Version: 1.16.1
Seed: 16327378876057492
Starting location: 18 63 27. Just generate a world with allow cheats to true, type in /tp 18 63 27 and make a savestate
Difficulty: Easy
Additional Information:
Glitched It is not allowed to manipulate the gear of zombies and skeletons (Or any other mob) to get op gear right at the start of the game.</description></item><item><title>Task 4</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/tas-comp/results/task4/</guid><description>Announced on 19.11.2021
Burnout%
Task: Make a redstone torch reach the burnout state
Version: 1.12.2
Seed: -8599623488174955388
Starting location: 0 79 0. (Should be no teleporting necessary)
Difficulty: Peaceful
Additional Information:
Glitchless The redstone torch has to be placed on top or on the side of bedrock It is a requirement that you play with the TorchBurnout mod uploaded below this message. This will send a chat message once a redstone torch is burned out.</description></item><item><title>Non Playback</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/tutorials/non-playback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/tutorials/non-playback/</guid><description>The basics Instead of choosing each input per frame and play back the TAS at the end, non-playback TASing is the act of screen recording yourself speedrunning, but setting the game to slow motion.
Later in video editing, you speed up the footage from slow motion to normal speed.
The result is a video in normal speed, but the player has better reaction times.
Additionally you may use savestates, which is the ability to create a restore point at any time during your run and if you fail at something, you can reload the savestate to try again.</description></item><item><title>Playback</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/tutorials/playback/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/tutorials/playback/</guid><description>What are playback TASes? Most TASes that you will see are made using some form of playback using an emulator with an option called movie playback which allows you to directly playback your TASes in real time.
Playback of these movies require no external tampering (e.g hacks/cheats), to run properly as it is the emulator/console reading a series of inputs from an input file like a player piano.
What are the benefits of playback TASing?</description></item><item><title>TASmod</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/downloads/playback/tasmod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/downloads/playback/tasmod/</guid><description>The main playback mod, currently only for version 1.12.2
Features Tickratechanger Tickrate 0/Pause server and client Item duplication (Duping) Fast Savestates</description></item><item><title>TASmod-OG</title><link>https://minecrafttas.com/downloads/playback/tasmod-og/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://minecrafttas.com/downloads/playback/tasmod-og/</guid><description>Experimental TASmod version for MC version 1.0</description></item></channel></rss>