<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation on Home</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/</link><description>Recent content in Installation on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup with Minecraft Launcher</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/setup_mclauncher/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/setup_mclauncher/</guid><description>MC version 1.14+ (For versions below 1.14 click here) We use the Fabric modloader for mods in 1.14+
Installing Fabric Download the installer from FabricMC. (Only download from this website!) Run the installer A window should appear Here you can select your Minecraft version as well as the Loader Version. The Loader should always be set to the newest version, some bugs may occur on old versions. Create Profile will automatically create a new profile in your Minecraft launcher.</description></item><item><title>Setup with MultiMC</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/setup_multimc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/setup_multimc/</guid><description>MultiMC is an open source Minecraft launcher with additional functionalities compared to the vanilla launcher
We suggest checking out the official Website
The main differences is that you can create multiple &amp;ldquo;instances&amp;rdquo; or minecraft, each with their own .minecraft/ folder. This means each instance can have a completely different minecraft installation, be it a different version, forge, fabric, different mods as opposed to only one mods folder in the vanilla launcher.</description></item><item><title>Java Setup</title><link>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/setup_java/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://test.minecrafttas.com/tutorials/installation/setup_java/</guid><description>Some Minecraft versions require different Java versions to run and for applications like MultiMC, you need to install java yourself.
By the time of writing this, Minecraft 1.18.2 is the latest version and the latest Java version is Java 18 (which is like a month old&amp;hellip; I will still use 17 for now)
Some things to point out:
The java requirements are: Minecraft up to 1.12.2 requires Java 8. Minecraft 1.</description></item></channel></rss>